Mohammad Hosein Kalantarian

Senior Android Developer

Phone: +989128667882 | +989355542971

Address: Gohardasht

Karaj, Alborz

Iran

Websites: www.MHKSoft.com | www.GitHub.com/MHKalantarian

Email: MHKalantarian@gmail.com

Software developer with 8+ years of experience in general & 4+ years of experience in Android mobile application development. 95%+ Crash free users on my apps according to Fabric.io

Team player, detail-oriented and dedicated to projects.

EXPERIENCE

Tosinso Co. April 2016 to December 2016

ORM Developer

Designed a custom ORM with C# language for the website

The company wanted to work with a customized ORM instead of Entity Framework & Hibernate

https://www.Tosinso.com/

PASK Co. December 2016 to April 2017

Junior Android Developer

Developed and designed several native project

Worked with team of 3 members

Key projects:

"Buffalo Burger - Food delivery"

"Akbar Jooje - Food delivery"

"Elevator City - Elevator parts shop"

NetDes Co. April 2017 to November 2017

Mid-level Android Developer

Developed and designed several native project

Worked with team of 5 members

Key projects:

"Service Car - Car service on-demand"

"iGol - Flower delivery"

"Santup - Home service on-demand"

"Appinew - General shop"

Karaj Islamic Azad University

Senior Android Developer

Developed and designed several native project

Worked with team of 12 members

Key projects:

"IKET - Hypermarket"

"Test Time - Trivia game"

"Benzini - Petrol delivery"

"Fan Baz - Technical service on-demand"

November 2017 to January 2019

Cafe Mive Startup

January 2019 - Present

Senior Android Developer / Project Manager

Developing and managing tech team in an awesome startup project for ordering fruits online.

The application has two sides which connects the fruit market directly to the customer with an immersive application on each side.

https://www.CafeeMive.com/

EDUCATION

Karaj Islamic Azad University (KIAU)

September 2015 to December 2019

Bachelor of Software Engineering

Score: 15

(0-20 Pointing System)

SKILLS

Soft skills

Problem solving, Communication, Ability to Work Under Pressure, Decision Making, Time Management, Leadership, Teamwork, Creativity

Programming languages

Java, Kotlin, Dart, C#, C++, C, VB, SQL, Freemarker

IDEs

Android Studio, Microsoft Visual Studio, Intellij Idea, Eclipse, SQL Server Management Studio

Data structures

XML, JSON

Essential android libraries

Android X, Material Components, Room Database, Socket.io, Retrofit, Butter Knife, Picasso, Glide, Timber, MP Charts

Designing softwares

Photoshop, Zeplin.io

LANGUAGES

Persian/Farsi (Native), English (Bilingual proficiency)